Enthusiastic professional with more than 1.3 years of experience in software engineering and application development. Effective worker and mentor and committed to leading exceptionally gifted teams. Ready to work closely with both teams and customers to identify most efficient and beneficial solutions for process improvement.

# **Work History**

2019-07 -Current

# **Software Engineer**

Mobinius Technologies, Bengaluru, Karnataka

- Maintained CAWI.Al which provides chatbot service, ensuring proper functioning for each client
- Used programming capabilities in JavaScript, MongoDB and Angular6 and other libraries as needed
- Communicated with customers to request information and ensure completion of work
- Managed escalated customer orders to meet aggressive deadlines and special orders
- Kept abreast of emerging technologies, software and trends and project applications
- Hands-on experience using UNIX and NGNIX web servers
- Hands-on experience deployment using GCP,HEROKU

2019-01 -2019-02

# Software Developer Intern

Mobinius Technologies, Bengaluru, Karnataka

- Introdused to various technologies, including Javascript, HTML5/CSS to develop website
- Learnt Basics of creating API's
- Developed and implemented online Bus Booking using SQL Server

# **Education**

2014-06 -2018-06

# **Computer Engineering**

Maharaja Institute of Technology - Mysore

# **Certifications**

2019-06 Data Analysis with Python by cognitiveclass.ai2019-10 MongoDB Aggregation Framework

# Vinayak Gaonkar

Software Engineer

## Contact

## **Address**

Nelepal Po: Mavinamane Tq: Yellapura (Uttara Kannada) Karnataka KA, 581337

## **Phone**

872 268 2638

## E-mail

vinayakgaonkarg@gmail.co m

#### LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in /vinayak-gaonkar-9725a214a

## **Skills**

Javascript

Very Good

Node.js

Very Good

MongoDB

Very Good

Angular 6

Good

SQL

Python

Average

Good